Thank you so much for watching!
It's a shadow cast upon yourself
We live through each other
Breathing the same air
Every cut, every bruise
Every whisper, despair
The world is a mirror
Reflecting your hand
The pain you give is the pain you'll understand
So try lightly
That's what grows.
You must be
Like a god, turn the wheel and warp the air
Every glance of sacred fraud, every breath of dare
A park beneath a watching moon, the stars align
They hum until the night unfolds, our silver skin we fall
Jock, this is Psycho Jogging.
Okay, I do have a, I mean, I do have a premier charisma. I do have a, I know it goes toberth, and we have a special
guest.
He's crazy. He's wonderful.
He's like the Willy Wonka of the panel versus if I wasn't, but so here's
for ghosts. I hope you like it.
To crush out
Ghost already did he took the whole crowd
That goes through the night
That's how you know the haunts alive
Lights flicker chats in the right
And somewhere goes, I'm about to die
Heroes are loud, like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes, keeping the scene
I was reborn may I have permission to crush
Psych is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
Turnin' pain into digital flame
May I have permission to crash out?
Dumb dumb to the ones who doubt
I don't know what's going on.
I try to tell him his song was on.
I don't know, he might be mad at me, I don't know.
Ghost, you know, he is temperamental a little bit.
Okay, there I am, my beautiful.
Oh, shit, I need my glass.
Oh, he wants my glasses on.
Ghost, I'm doing the show.
I was literally premiering your video.
I don't know, he's confused.
Don't rewind it.
Is it okay?
I don't know.
You look wiki. Okay. Oh
Good Lord
Whenever I try to do something nice everything goes wrong
Okay, well
I'm Alexander McQueen you're in trouble
For doxing
Okay Alexander McQueen dox easy and stuff like I'm just giving his address. He's giving his mom's name Alex. No, I had to end the show
Plus that's not right. Plus I got a privacy complaint already. Okay, and it's so it's like, you know
Why are you fucking with my show like you're not supposed to be doing that? So you're definitely find
$25 because the porn bomb yesterday and then the doxing today
If you want to come on panel
Yeah, dude, yeah, pay the fine do the crime pay the fine. I don't want to be an asshole about it, but
Like the job. Thank you
Alex come on, this is my life, you know, it's like
Fuck it's bad enough
they were talking about, you know, trafficking,
COCA, INE all over the country,
like in doing things to enterprise rent a car.
I don't even want to get into what they were talking about.
Otto and, Otto and, and Alexander.
But Alex, if you're out there listening,
and you're in trouble, you're lucky it's just 25.
I could have doubled it to 50, but trying to,
You're reasonable, okay, but seriously those both could have hurt my channel a lot if I wasn't so
Fast I'm fixing it, but
Hey, hey, yeah, it's good school donkey dear. Hope you're okay. Oh, hon. It's good school donkey
What are you calling it donkey?
Shrek, I'm just kidding. Hold on a Apollo more Moyan labs. That's not the real Apollo Moulin. Maybe I
Don't know there's Apollo moon something
Alex is sleeping. Okay mess of
headache a
little bit of a
cocaine
Coca-Cola crash out is that caffeine, right?
Um, wow, I know actually like Otto's like, oh just come over to Canada. Okay. Oh, okay
Here he comes
Here you come. Oh donkey. I know it donkey me. Oh, okay. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. I knew it
I know donkey. I thought you were quoting Shrek to me bonkae. Oh
You like do you like it? Do you see it? I think it was pretty good. Here's the link. Here we go
There you go. Invite guests coffee
Yeah
Posted I
Like it I did put a little bit of Hindu into into song and it worked it worked. I think it like made it like
Exciting arbiters goes by the way, you don't know. Oh, you liked it. Okay good
Well, oh, we got a world Canadian mounted police in the chat. What's going on here?
Yo guys, what's going on? What the fuck?
Fuck what where do you why are you? Why are you now you're a fake cop too? Yeah
You're copying Alexander taking a page from his playbook
No, that was just the other day. I was playing with him. You're just playing with him. Well, Alexander
Go see you like the video did you see the video? Oh
You did
Yeah, a little bit. Okay, you didn't like it or no or what I
Think it was pretty cool
You got full, you know, I did spend all my credits
Are you ready to crash that's what the song is called it's called a permission to crash out
I didn't see it. Can you play it again? Can I play it again? Yes. Yeah, please enjoy guys fucking the fucking
Permission to crush out
Ghost already did he took the whole crowd let's fucking go
That's how you know, the haunts are live
Lights flicker, chats in the ride
And somewhere goes about to die
Heroes are loud, like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Let's fucking go
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
I remember, I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
Ghost already did, he took the whole crowd
Heart of gold, voice of fire
When ghost shows up, the stakes get higher
Dum dum, that's his war cry sound
Every hater gets fun right round
North fucking gold!
He brings it loud
Psyche is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
In a world full of clowns, he's the last to fake
When the screen went dark, he kept me awake
All the noise fades, but ghost remains
Turning pain into digital flame
May I have permission to crash out?
Dumb dumb to the ones who doubt
What a beautiful fucking song what a beautiful song you like that
Thank you. You're welcome
beautiful
Good job
I
Loved it. And what do you think?
But that's what I love it you loved it. Let me get it off the screen. So I love it a beautiful song
Where are we here?
There we are. Okay. Yeah
that yeah, I did that with some
Chappy ready this day. I don't know. He runs. Yeah ghost runs. It's a ghost is like Donnery mayor of a psyche burst. I
Don't know what that means. I know that was a beautiful song
well, I
Put my heart into it for you. So
Beautiful song
Enjoy. I don't know if you liked like the Hindu. I really like I've been really into Hindu
Indu say hey, there's Jamie's cowboy. That one was looking for you
You know what? She happy running the state. I don't know about that. I think that that means my name
I do love my chat, but you know
Some of the chat like last night was pretty pretty horrendous, you know, sir. I would like to bless you real quick if you don't mind
Thank you
Beautiful song pretty much
Oh, um
But what Athens come on
Where have you been Athens? I haven't seen Athens for a while. Are you mad at me at that?
I don't know everyone's mad at me for a little bit, and I
Don't know I don't think you were talking shit about me
School bathens is in the chat. Yeah, no way
Yep, yep, yep, yep. Oh he is overtime at work. Okay
Well, it's good. I think I mean I get and you know, I made a cute little song that like, you know
I think beat and I are like maybe
Gonna make up or whatever, but you know, I think where we already like I don't think we're mad at each other anymore
but
You know, I did post something and then it's this guy named what's his name?
Moshe or something which is like means Moses
He's always the guy that's always like oh on King David blah blah
He wrote me like a really rude thing like oh, you don't even know what love is you're just living in some fantasy world
You don't even know this person. Oh, hey, you don't know what you're talking about. I mean, it's like that is a very
People just like like to write these myths about the psyche burst, right like and
Like the truth about things like it like I did no beta for probably six months before
You're gonna go check your email six months before, you know
Oh, thank you ghosts. Thank you for the beautiful donation. I appreciate you
Yep, and Alexander McQueen if you're around you're in trouble, mister, and you're being fined because you got me
Privacy warning you got me
porn porn bomb yesterday
you're you're um
You're gonna need to pay a little fine
keeping it reasonable for you Alex, but
I was the enemy queen, but anyway, yeah, Moshe, you don't know what you're talking about on King David. Okay on King David
you don't know what you're talking about and
And everything's gonna be okay little snack here
Here's oh, oh Alex you can't come on the house, you know, here's what you need to do Alex and get the Zell ready
Ghost where'd you go?
Ghosts just dropped a 10 chat. Thank you Alex 25 bucks because you got me a
Privacy warning from for doxing easy and his mom and everything and then yesterday you pour them on me
And I was gonna let the form on go, but then you just uh-oh then but then you keep going so
You can let me know in the back chat if you're going to
you know, pay the fine, do the time.
Is that really School of Athens?
I believe it is.
He's modded, right?
Oh, no, he's not modded,
but I believe it's School of Athens.
He talks like School of Athens.
I recognize the, I will mod you,
but you haven't been around for,
he hasn't been long since I unmodded everybody
because another thing Alex did when he,
Alex,
Chase tried to chase away Guacamole Guadalupe who actually, you know, give you donations and
and
Got a reading and like was really kind of very sweet sweet little avocado lady
It's in the back shot Alice when we see home
Yeah, okay, he's gonna okay, Alex. Thank you Alice. I appreciate you. No, I'll let you on this
You help me out with that now really help me out this week, too. That was a beautiful song
Thank you, and I hope you let you play that for you play that forever. That's that's that's your in your school of Athens link
Yeah, the way he talks to Jamie at school and Jamie Jamie and school have a little special relationship and
For sure
This goes sober let's go sober fast
So enjoying your new mic
I'm wearing my
My my uh, I just was a small goth's trash. I don't know why
just like
Needless, so you must make me cry
Oh, I was like I did why did want to like make it like touching like you know cuz um
We should have done dumb. I did you can dumb dumb you hear that part is it he goes dumb
dumb. I didn't hear that. You should have played it. I said it twice. Yeah. The dumb dumb
made it into the song. The. I didn't hear that part. Yeah. It goes dumb dumb. You're super
aww. So here's an analogy for you. Miranda Kerr is sort of Victoria's Secret is so I don't
I don't know, Jamie, are you an Abercrombie model?
I used to have, there used to be an Abercrombie.
That was Tricks.
And guys, and then Pie came back, my little Pie cat.
Can you put on the old Ghost song?
Thank you, Ghost, I won't forget.
Yes, I will, I will.
Yeah!
Thank you, Ghost.
I won't forget you.
Oh, I mean, you don't, I mean, play it.
Okay, let me see.
Can you please put it on?
You don't mind, brother.
Sure.
Let's gooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
I also have a fancy boat
and everything is dancing
I want to prohibit you
make sure not to have your face turned black
what?
always look back
make sure not to have your face turned black
and here's to you
I also have a fancy boat
The only big part is to get back to the car.
That's me.
Okay, I was on the screen and he was on the phone for a minute.
Thank you ghost, I won't forgive you
Come on for me
You make me laugh till my face turns blue
So you're so boring
You're funny as hell, yeah, it's always a blast
These moments we're making are built to last
Thank you ghost, I'm one of a kind
I'm one of a kind
beautiful song
God, I love it. I just look process passing around
That's a small price to pay actually for all the trouble
Actually
What are the team
The Yankees I will
Hey, do you hear J dog went to a gay bar and dance last night? I am a Yankee fan
Ass on stream last night when we got fucking
What was he doing the mula now say so you can go to the store because obviously these sticks don't realize that when they cash
When ghost drops on jedda's he's not gonna get that for a month ghost, okay?
So it's better to sell it. I'm pretty sure you have happened
Well, yeah
He might not be alive in a month. They go say it starts like every month over again. So it's like
Ghost you're wasting it because YouTube takes half of it see like now when I'm gonna sell site 25 hours
He's gonna get the whole 25
when you
You know what it's fun to have cash apps and probably YouTube looks at me kind of it is
You know what Alex you made my mind up awesome. No more money
Fuck you fuck you Alex, but you know what but you know what's funny. Um, yeah, like um
they
Yeah, they
Because they're making money too because you know so because they're making so it's like probably is good for my show
Cuz I I've done like a lot of stuff
like no more money I know ghost nice to see your name on the screen like
arbitrator donated now you owe 50 hours because now it now it now you've been
15 $50 no more money what the hell that I'm not gonna I'm just gonna say you're
I didn't have I mean
50 Jesus just like that boom
Well now it now you're
I'll forget you but I'm not seeing no more money and I'm gonna do 30
I'm not the rich man. You know, you
Started would you like to give?
You know what? I got you. So I'll give you five. I'll give you five. I got you. But I got to drop off to go to sell
All right, I appreciate you. Um Alex. Thank you so much
Give me two seconds, buddy. Thank you. Okay. Um, and that does really help me this week because a little bit. Um
I uh
I started a little bit behind and stuff, but yeah, it's okay. Nothing to worry about. I'm I'm always like, okay
I'm always like able to somehow manage, you know, all this time. I'm just I always able to
But that I do like, you know, I
do spend a
So it just depends. I've been eating McDonald's a lot. I'll just put it that way
I'm claiming McDonald's monopoly game, which I love it's McDonald's expensive, but on the app
Trust me get the monopoly game play the app
Um, and it's like you'll get a lot of free food. I have like so much free food. It's crazy. So
Yeah, coffee. Oh, I have a coffee in the fridge, too
Okay
Whoo, yeah, I only thought and then McDonald's is like they put out my stuff in a little nice trays
Like they put the straw. They know exactly what to do. So this yeah, we're good fucking ghost. No, it's cool
They left us alone. I think we're alone now
Was your girlfriend mad about last night was she mad
Uh-huh. Oh, thank you Arbiter about what? No, nothing cuz I was hitting on you. Maybe no, I mean I wasn't really
I didn't notice you didn't notice
Memories that's what you kissed me if you could you said you picked on the cheek. You seem to really remember that
I do I do I have it in my diary
I've written it down and
Thank you ghost, thank you ghost
My journal entries. Oh
Thank you, Alex. Thank you Alex and Alex Alex to keep his word. And so I appreciate you Alex. Thank you very much
Thank you that really does help me out right now
Appreciate you all
Oh, and yeah, and also, you know, I will be able to again like put some
Put some of this a lot of it back into the show and the show will just improve
And so you can think goes for the the show has already improved so much just with my
with my mall got t-shirt being able to use the computer. Yeah, I'm all got the trash being able to use the computer
Makes it so good because now I can edit the
Stuff on YouTube much it's much easier and also just do the AI stuff much better like faster and just it's just much better
Do you remember that conversation we had last night?
Yeah
What happened? Uh-oh. Oh, yeah, here you're here. Here are the woman. Oh, you and your talk. Oh, are you near torta?
Or does your kids tart?
I mean, it's a fan of fish
You need your talk. Go ahead
That's the name of um big yos is here now. You're back in the second
That's a scribble scribbles his brother's name of torta. Okay. Hold on a second. No torta
I don't hear what I know.
What can you do?
No, I didn't.
I need to fix my hair. Hold on.
Who the fuck are you talking to?
Thank you, Alex. You're all, you're, you paid your fine.
And you are...
I'm almost tempted to mod you, but that would have cost the extra, but, you know...
Can I get modded?
Of course you're already a mod aren't you? No
Are you know you're oh, you're not a you are look see the wrench
Hey
We run with her
Go ahead here. I'll sip away
Back to the kitchen. Let me run one
Thank you those
God damn this mission seeming to ideally catch me she fucking everything up
Do you know how to get a plate out of the sink no
It's not that hard I can help you actually I'll help you lift up to play
Yeah, I was listening and back to the kids
To return you know, I can put it in small words for you
Let me have the conversation with it
by the way, I'm glad your girl gave you permission to be here.
Good to have you here.
Come on, why don't you fuck off and why don't you be a good boy?
You a good boy? Why don't you fuck off?
Why don't you be ghost?
Why don't you fuck off is what I'm saying.
Why don't you fuck off?
We're making some dinner here.
What'd you like to run one? Yes?
I don't mean to interrupt but I just saw something interesting Donald Trump Donald Trump's uh, he eats McDonald's every day
Okay, and here's what he eats. He has a cool. Hey big Mac
Pounder on fries
And yeah an orange Fanta
He has three burgers fries and orange Fanta. Wow
every day. Every day. Uh it's
me telling you not to do that.
and it's now it's in a calorie.
I'm going to disappear. I'll
be I'll be gone. Okay, here you
talk. You talk guys. I'm going
to talk to you now. Where am I
under now? I don't think that's
really all of Athens.
Yo, yo, yo, Alexander, moving
How's your torque?
Matter of fact, how are you doing sir? I think that's school
He's like Canada. Can I can I not talk to you? How are you doing?
Candidates, right? Oh, that's you send me a text
What's your number, bro? I'll text you. How are you doing?
How are you doing?
Did you know let me ask you a question. Let's go still work. I
Didn't know yet
Okay, cool. You're just gonna be a fucking fake. What's your problem? Why are you so upset?
Stop the fuck
Why are you so upset?
No, we're not doing you right over here. That's why I think
Why are you so upset for
Summer I think someone pretending to be you know what you know you you know you said say you said he's sorry to go
I'll let it go. Do you say sorry? I'll let it go. I
Think that's fair. Okay, sorry
you should say sorry to you bitch
but you should say sorry
can I get an apology or no
but why
I want an apology sir
if you were in school he wouldn't be trying to prove this
I wasn't talking to you don't fuck
I was talking to Canada don't fuck
I want an apology
Yeah, school hasn't texted me. I don't think that's it. I
Want an apology? Let's go sober. I want a policy
Canada says say sorry
Or you can bring it on the ass fucking dumbass fucking retarded girlfriend on here
I'll burn her up as well. Oh, you could also just say sorry.
That's kind of fine. I'm gonna fuck you up for nothing. I'm gonna fuck you up for nothing.
Listen, ma'am. Are you gonna say sorry or I'm gonna burn her up? I just said sorry.
Say sorry, guys. He's drinking. Say sorry. No, no, say sorry, guys. No.
Say sorry mr. Ghost you better say it
I'll do you one better. Yep, go ahead
You I'm a deal you sit the bomb I'm gonna do you on better you suck it
Give me one better go ahead
Can I get can I talk to you in your talk top?
You just you know what sir? I'll give you I'll give you one. I'm ghost is ghost is so
Loving I'll give you a bit. You just hit the ball. Go ahead
You go get that what I'm saying
Summer I know how school writes, too, but it almost looks like you say
Say it say your story goes
Where am I or me to catch up so say you sorry goes you're gonna say you're sorry. I'm on a crash
I'm giving you one more chance to say sorry again do it
All right
Okay, I'm going to crash outside.
Just want to fuck your set man, silence.
Don't look at fucking talking about him.
His fat ass girlfriend, little fat fuck.
Don't look at fucking talking about
you need a little fat girlfriend.
Put her on camera again, dude.
You know what the fuck you're talking about.
Yeah, I have no idea what you're talking about.
Nobody's not in the big house.
Okay, go ahead.
You and your torta.
Go ahead.
You need a little fat fucking girlfriend.
Put it on camera again. That's four top put her again
Yeah, you fat as fuck yeah, you fat as fuck girl. Don't talk to me like that
By the way, you're never in fucking mr. Ghost like that
You found a song girl you buy you least 200 pounds
Are you not 200 pounds
You know what the fuck you're talking about you just didn't fuck up
Don't always wins Augusto bros go
For top
Fucking all right camera camera actually I saw you camera you know
You girls that you retard and your rows are tired
You would you like to argue brother? I
Don't want to say fat she's um at least 30 pounds over the fucking
She's at least a beast here
Yeah, I came though you want to run one you want to sit there and shut the hook up
God damn it feels good to run this Canada do you want to run one? I
Won't talk about your status girlfriend. I'll just talk about you sir. I
Think boys up there and good boys up there and shut the fuck up your
You think what I think the follow is saying summer that you aren't a blind follower
Can I talk to your fat ass girlfriend stop ghost
If he asked me nicely, I will stop
But you say please please stop ghost
Where did everybody go
Just me brother, I guess
No, it's like though
By the way, I came back to nothing this time to apologize to your girl like she probably would what my ass in the debate she probably a better
Uh fucking she probably plays better than me and like Martin was there. I don't miss your poem. It's fucking shit
Sorry
No, stop slapping those lips together
I'm eating some fruit
What everybody fucking go this is so weird
Ass was like
I'll call him
By the way, I hope you're all realized like I didn't mean that
Be good
He was just being outrageous. He's trying to be he I saw oh you jump scared stop doing that
Stop doing that
Yeah, well, that's why she did have something to say I think came to the fucking retard think his girls are also a fucking retard
Dumb dogs
No, if anybody wants to run it with big gos, I'm here. I'm Bender room
It goes to where let's go this room
there we go
There's a linky
Oh, we guess is gonna join
And don't call it a linky
Can't talk to your torta
Candles, you don't mind you talk to your total
My bitch released about 30 pounds of weight
Sorry
You know what I should kick you out. Yeah, you're not gonna say nothing. You're soon. It's up there and try to fuck up
Good boy
No, so I can't you don't say I'm good. I'm very good
You know you haven't any of my fun. How do you want to focus focus?
No, Victoria J
No
She is a very obnoxious
sounding
Woman on IP to she's on up. She's on beta's panel yelling a blogger right now. Well, okay. Just you want to come up around once
You should we want to go over to betas and like see what's going on in there?
Nope, I want them to come over here. Oh
They can't take me over here
Be this running a show I
Know I was just there
They can't meet me over here though. Did you hear the woman with the like that accent? Hi. I'm before you Jay
Oh, and her name is like what's her name on this game? I mean, she's just a beautiful man right there
Sexy man, okay, we're talking to me
Listen, I'm good
That's a good looking man, I'll tell you
There we go
Let me meet myself. Let me meet myself before I fucking
Okay, ghost you're up. Let's see. So, let's see look
Let's see
Well guys, what do I have to tell you? Okay, so today is
Sunday, can you can you say you love us? I?
Love all of you. I
Love you say it like you mean it. I
Love you
You said what stay it like you mean it
No
I love you
No, that's a beautiful man here. I'll tell you that
Let's go down here. I'm seeing I'm seeing
Sir, if you want this channel pretty pretty much dead if you want to run to a different channel
I'm down to let's run one
Okay, I'm just saying because it's like, you know
Oh
We can come back here, we can just like go like I don't think
I think he was hurt
Canada, well, you know, you
Your roots is girlfriend
Fucking
You know they did you know what honestly it's like they did talk a lot of shit about kids
They're talking a lot of shit about his woman, but he teeth are here, so I'll give him credit. He's growing on me. Oh
He is beautiful man beautiful man
Beautiful for time yard
Now
Is anybody else gonna fucking going to panel
Fuckin ghost sober for what reason nobody's join
Well, you know cuz it's like I think
People are just overwhelmed by it by me
You piece of shit you should
Can somebody get $10 oh
No
Just get off it. This is waste of time. Okay. It's not fun. There's a fucking alcoholic there. Okay
It's happening. It's happening. It's not fun. Okay
I'm sorry. I'm sorry guys. I may uh
I tried my best. Um, let's see. Yeah, okay. Let's go to beat us and see what's going on
Cuz you know what I miss you Peter. Oh my gosh
I thought you and be the were on the outs
Well, we have more ups and downs than you know Magic Mountain basically, but I think we're okay
I think we'll be okay. I just don't I I
Don't know I'm trying
But you know what Canada you have a very lovely girlfriend. I'm sorry. I don't I don't mean to like let
You know
Herbita's bears. I think he was kid. I think he's just being silly, right?
You kind of sound like a retort ma'am okay ghost can I run one with her?
Yeah, she doesn't want to run with you. I think she's I want to run one. She's not having fun
That's it with that. He's doing a dumbass bitch like that. Oh, okay. It goes
Sorry
She don't know what the fuck she's well. I'm being rude. She don't know what the fuck she's talking about
How about let's go over to let's go over and beat it and see what's going on there
Cuz I think that there's some weird stuff
Well, no, we have happens we have a lot of people in the chat that want to join
But no one's come up
You have to give the permission brother you have permission everyone come up. Please please please come up
Yeah, after all these New York people please come up. It was a fun panel earlier
Sorry, I'm sorry. It'll be fun again. I'm fine. It was a fun panel earlier
I think it will be fun in the middle of the night. I think it's like it takes the middle of the night
Oh, do you want to do when I go on her? Why are you gonna talk to you privately, bro?
Okay, gosh, I'm really you want to go there
She's mad now. I'm now I'm getting upset. Yeah torches. I'm gonna fuck up me some more years. I'm gonna go
I'm going to beat us and I'll be back though. I love you guys. I'll be back. Okay, let's go
I'm not going to leave. I'm going to end the stream and I'll come back and I'll come back after I'm going to go. Maybe going. Let's see. Let's see what's up with her. Well, let's go stop her. Don't like you thinking about that. We're going to have ghost over in her chat too. She's going to celebrate. Okay, cool. We can do that.
How's
Lonnie, oh look Tony Bologna. What up? He left us here alone. What a bitch. What a dick
What a fucking retard what a bitch?
Well, what about he left he went to beat us by the way school of
Dollars can ask me one question. How much money did I give this guy like ten million dollars?
Since since you started like a few months ago like 10 million now. I mean in the past
Oh today, I don't know boy. So I don't count
Ones ghost
nah fuck that we don't want to fuck that you don't want to spend all that money right fuck that pussy
what i keep talking about yeah i'm trying to i'm just trying to have fun
nah you fucked up
yeah it's going away from seven four fifty dollars in time
I'll be back
I do I do I do want to please so go take go go. You know what?
Make my McDonald's and chill with the chat right what McDonald's where everyone's a little bit everyone's a little bit
I've been more money dick. You said you like had a rough week or something because you're not gonna get the superchass for a month
It's okay. It's okay. So
If you need a little more, just tell me I will sell you school of Athens wants to give you $50
I'm gonna have you to text me. I just leave beta alone and I GGR is what the text message says now
I'm feeling like going over
Not just nothing or anything just to be nice bring someone up bring someone up and go to beat us
Don't leave me here alone. I mean you can if you want, but no, I'm not gonna know
I'm gonna say I'm gonna say and then he says wow and he says wow. Yeah, I'm gonna tell on you Tony
I know who it is. Yeah, no, I was out always smile always smile
Wow, I fell the n-word. Well, you you spelled it out
Letters on my big Tony baloney
I'm a racist shit
You're so silly. God's here more manure. Oh, I need some my garden manure manure. Oh my god. It's black or G by the way
Psych. Thank you. Thank you. Good. It's black or G
manure I
called him earlier on some other panel making fun
And he's threatening you now Alex
I live for training I live for it who
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Tony Tony ghost. You're not Tony. Are you man? If I find out you
Choked a choo-choo train right at you, bro leaving his own fucking
Random guy comes up here like he's not Tony. Let's start God in November. That's so weird to me
Daddy by the way, it's another one
Someone go to be this if not, I'm gonna go there
Oh, I don't know beat it was live. Okay. I'll see you guys be and be there. I was with Sam and Sam, and then
Well, can I go live?
No, those give me a thousand dollars. I can I go over there. I'll send a cross job. What what?
I'll send a cross job
Right now that comes up here like he's the guy on the couch
Hey, it's a ghost I'm still going with it. Yeah, Tony is
Okay, don't you like throwing a mule around? How about giving him instantly see my
I
Wifey ending goes to over don't turn to end it. How are you gonna end this over? You can go to be this leave us up here alone
This is ghost this final bell calm down
I'm here. I'm here. The Joseph stress me the fuck out. I was like I wanted to like
Remember ghost you always like go go to be that's going on her panel going her panel and I never wanted you and now I'm like, okay
Well, Victoria J's up there sounding like it in maniac. Oh
Go man, do what you gotta do, do what you gotta do and it will make you happy.
a little bit. She's so cute with that dumb voice.
Say hi. Say hi.
Did you just leave?
I didn't leave. I didn't leave.
I didn't leave.
Stop fucking around.
Stop fucking around. Go handle your business, dude.
I'm not going to go over there because I've already been...
Go in there like you own the place.
Exactly.
That's how you gotta live life, bro.
Because people don't know if you own it or not.
You have to walk through the venue like you own the shit.
If she puts you backstage just laugh at her and leave
Go cook blogger. I can go cook a good blogger. Oh my god bloggers up there. That's fucking Lionel Thundercatch. Oh
He looks like Lionel, bro, right with their hair fucking hauling oats
That's right. You just reminded me. I was up there calling him Lionel. I called think that is Pantel
I said be it was Chittaro. I was just going crazy up there. You just reminded me
No, and I called someone mumra
Christine the mummy, you know mum rule. I was like
Yo yo yo
huh your shit bomb again shit bomb you know who did that bro I think DJ Electra DJ Electra
made fun of it listen to me guys after that happened last night DJ Electra we were on
another panel and she was like well at least now you know you can get the shit fucked out of you
and started laughing hysterical I traced it back to fucking British so what is that who makes fun of
I was making hours like you I can't believe psyche just got poem bomb with a cock and shit and DJ Electra goes
Well, at least now, you know, you can get the shit fucked out of you and started laughing hysterical
I was like, it was you don't bitch. It was you
No, but think about it, man
That's crazy. I don't think she'd be into that shit
Yeah
Yo, it was you God wasn't it you fucking freak
I'm upset that she would do that